<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Blocking Tracker</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="title_activity_set_view">SetView</string>
    <string name="change_Script">Change Script</string>
    <string name="change_Floorplan">Change Floorplan</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="title_activity_about">About</string>
    <string name="about_text">
        "Throughout the course of a rehearsal process, Stage Managers need to record the "
        "blocking/choreography of scenes as the directors and actors stage them. This process "
        "is highly tedious on paper and often is slower than the pace of rehearsal. Furthermore, "
        "the staging will often go through many revisions, which can clutter a paper record with "
        "several edits.\n\n"

        "Blocking Tracker makes the beleaguered Stage Manager’s life easier. "
        "Instead of countless pages of half-erased pencil marks and scratched-out directions, "
        "we provide a simple image template onto which actor blocking can be recorded simply "
        "and efficiently, using modular icons that can be changed with ease.\n\n"

        "Blocking Tracker is the creation of Ben Fuligni and Selena Groh for Tufts University’s "
        "Mobile Development course (Fall 2017) taught by Ming Chow. "
        "Much gratitude and acknowledgement to Ming Chow and our fellow students.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_script_instructions">Script Instructions</string>
    <string name="script_instructions_text">
        "To add new blocking:\n"
        "1. Highlight the portion of text which is associated with the blocking.\n"
        "2. Press the \"Track Blocking\" button. This will take you to the blocking page, where you can record the actors' positions at that moment.\n"
        "\nTo revisit previously entered blocking:\n"
        "1. Highlight just the footnote in the script associated with the blocking. For instance, \"[1]\".\n"
        "2. Press the \"Track Blocking\" button. This will take you to the blocking associated with that footnote.\n"
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_set_instructions">Set Instructions</string>
    <string name="set_instructions_text">
        "To add a new actor dot:\n"
        "Press the \"+\" button and enter an actor label. By default, the actor dot appears in the top left.\n"
        "\nTo move an actor dot:\n"
        "Tap once on a dot to select it (it will change colors when selected), then tap again where you want to move it.\n"
        "\nTo delete an actor dot:\n"
        "Tap once on a dot to select it (it will change colors when selected), then press the trash can icon to delete it.\n"
        "\nTo save the blocking and return to the script:\n"
        "Press the save icon to save the dots' positions where they currently are, and associate them with the selected point in the script.\n"
    </string>
</resources>
